Okay, today's video is called one cat and four catsuits because I have one cat
This is Nono. Hello! And I have four catsuits for my headmeat and she's going to choose
She's going to choose
The order in which I'm going to wear the catsuits. I got these four catsuits. Thanks to my lovely followers and
Yeah, I got the cat with me. Let's do the selection. Alright, I'm going to put some treats on the four boxes and whichever
she chooses first I'm going to try on first okay okay this one apparently
and this second
She's so blind.
You're fine.
This was the first one.
So I'm going to get changed.
First catsuit.
And I decided to put some gloves on.
Which I cut.
Like I cut the ends off one day because they were too short.
And I thought, well, this is also cool.
so I took a pair of scissors and that's their look now. The back is really
interesting it has a lacing in the back
which is really playful overall I think the design with the short arms is really
like playful and cute and together with lacing in the back it's a nice design
you don't think like from the front that it's some kind of special catsuit
whatever but then turning around it's like woo! cat is sitting right there and watching me
I think she's judging me what I like is that the legs are really long and it
fits really good. Whoops, sorry. Lost my footing for a moment. I am wearing size small and now
I'm going to change into the next one. So this is next. I'm just reading the washing and wearing
instructions that came with the cat suit and it says it is elastic but please choose the correct
size to prevent unnecessary over stretching so even if it's a stretchy fabric always all the
true to size and also did you know that the hidden zippers are called french zippers that's what i
learned today anyway this is the catsuit and i think it is the most fetish catsuit i've seen
from no handmade not only does it have a crotch zipper but there are also zippers here in the
area which of course only show my bra at the moment but imagine if you are not
wearing a bra underneath then the fun starts anyway this is very very playful
again otherwise design is rather simple I like the ring here in front that's a
nice touch and also that there is kind of a belt imitation in the shape here
now what do I have for black no handmade catsuits it's all started when I saw
that they were on sale I paid around about 50 bucks for a catsuit and so I
asked my patrons and my youtube community hey if you want to help me buy
some of them then I can make a video so I opened my coffee again and said let's
do it and my plan was initially to get two of them but after a short while I
was able to buy all four of them so thanks a lot to my community all right
onto the next one and the cat chose this one also I think because I tapped on the
box so my problem is it is a snake pattern or a textured fabric and it does
look rather similar than this one so if I'm going to change no one who will
scroll through the video will see any difference so I'm overruling the cat and
say I'm going to try this one next a unique design we have like a body suit
part in the middle but bust free and of course I'm playing it safe for YouTube
and I'm wearing my bra. If I would wear it to a party I just put on some pasties
or nothing underneath. Also for the backside we have the wow effect again
because there is this lacing again. Let me check it out, really cute.
nice and if you're part of the gothic scene you know that cheap flimsy lace fabric
this is not it this is like um really soft not as stretchy but a bit thicker and feels like
really high quality fabric also you have different textures so it's really really cool fabric I
really like it it feels really nice I like it I think this is my favorite so far from the three
I've shown yeah because it's nice with the lace yeah have a look at the lace again you know this
would be the perfect suit to wear to a kind of masquerade ball where you put on these kind of
eye only masks the lacy ones I think that would be perfect combination
final catsuit by the way the cat disappeared again I don't know I think she's hungry and
grumpy because it's raining all day anyway I'm going to go change for the last time
Okay, final cat suit.
And the cat is here again because I'm again bribing her with treats.
And this is the snake fabric.
Snake... sorry I can't concentrate, I have to watch the cat.
Snake textured fabric, that is what I wanted to say on the last treat.
I paired her with red heels and I have a red back here.
Here it's like this.
You're not impressed at all, right?
Do you have more treats?
No, I don't.
This catsuit has a three-way zip.
So there's one zipper zip, whatever you call the handle grab-on to the thingy.
And we have two more which are here currently.
zipper runs through the whole catsuit until here in the back by cat. The
advantage of a front zipper is in my opinion that there's no zipper in the
back obviously but this means that you can bend over and there is no unstretchy
zipper preventing you from like being flexible enough. That's what I always
hate about back zippers that you can't do this because they're not stretchy and
Anyway, and the other advantage is that you of course have nice boots in front of catsuits. Of course I could close it as well. The fabric is quite firm. It's also thicker than the normal wet look fabric.
I don't know if you can really see the pattern here or the texture. It's kind of
snaky. Anyway that was today's video. I hope you enjoyed it. Thanks again for the
catsuits and tell me in the comments which one was your favorite. I think I'd
I'd still go with the lacy one because that was cute and it's not something I have in
my closet already.
If you want to see behind the scenes or more pictures, check out my Patreon.
We have a nice community there and I post a lot there, a lot of additional content.
And leave a thumbs up, subscribe to my channel here.
Have a nice day.
Bye!